Hello, Hall and Wood Finance, Phil speaking, how can I help?
Hi there, I just want to see what my overdraft limit is actually.
Um, yep, have you got the account number?
Yeah, so it's 1-2.
1-2.
Oh, sorry, sorry, it's C-F.
Oh, sorry, C-F.
1-2.
3-4.
5-5.
Okay, hold on one second.
Is that Lisa Jennings?
That's the one.
Okay, great, and you just wanted to know what, sorry?
Just how much my overdraft limit is actually.
Okay, just hold on one sec.
Okay, so you've got a limit of a thousand pounds,
but then you've got 150 pounds of emergency borrowing.
So basically if you go beyond that thousand pounds,
you can borrow 150 in emergency,
but you do get higher charges with it.
That's okay, that's fine.
Thank you very much.
All right, see you later.
Bye.